Guide to the Karen Swenson Papers MSS.069
Fales Library and Special Collections
Karen Swenson Papers
1945-2002
1974-1999
Fales Library and Special Collections
Swenson, Karen
MSS.069
11 Linear Feet in 14 manuscript boxes, 5 record cartons, and 1 card box
Karen Swenson (born 1936) is an American poet, educator, and journalist. Born in New York City, Swenson attended Barnard College and New York University. She taught for fifteen years at City University in New York and is a celebrated published author and world traveler. The collection dates between 1945 and 2002, with the bulk dating between 1974 and 1994. Materials include literary journals and print publications, newspaper and magazine articles; correspondence; poems; photocopied manuscripts; photographs; and four audiocassettes.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedure
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596, with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Karen Swenson in 1996; accretion donated in 2005. Accession numbers related to the donations are 1996.069 and 2005.069.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in the following series, with each series arranged at the folder level, in alphabetical order by topic:
Series I. Clippings
Series II. Correspondence
Series III. Ephemera
Series IV. Poetry
Series V. Photographs
Series VI. Printed Publications
Biographical / Historical
Karen Swenson (born 1936) is an American poet, educator, and journalist. Swenson was born in New York City and grew up in Chappaqua, New York. She attended Barnard College and New York University, and was a poet in residence at Skidmore College, University of Idaho, Denver University, Clark University, Scripps College, and Barnard College. She taught for fifteen years at City University in New York and is a celebrated published author and world traveler. Swenson wrote of her travels for The New York Times, The Wall Street Journal, The New Leader, and several magazines.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of materials created by Karen Swenson that document her personal and professional interests throughout her career as an American poet, educator, and journalist. Materials include printed publications, correspondence, clippings, ephemera, poetry, and photographs. The printed publications from Swenson's personal library include inscribed literary journals and books that she collected between 1973 and 2002. The correspondence files include professional and personal letters, postcards, and greeting cards written to and from Swenson between 1963 and 1985, some featuring her poems. Many letters to Swenson include analysis of specific poems she sent to friends and colleagues. The bulk of the collection includes Swenson's typed and handwritten poems, and photocopied manuscripts of published poems between 1945 and 2002. Most of the poems are undated and include Swenson's handwritten annotations.
Separated Materials
Printed publications selected for deacession will be reviewed by the curator and added to the Library collection or the Library's duplicates collection.
American poetry -- 20th century.; Authors, American -- 20th century.; Poets, American -- 20th century -- Correspondence.; Photographs.; Clippings (information artifacts); Correspondence.; Poems.; Publications (documents); Sound recordings.; Swenson, Karen
- Series I: Clippings, 1973-1990
  Scope and Contents
  This series includes photocopied magazine articles, and original and photocopied newspaper articles.
  - "Beyond the Killing Fields" in "Dance" October 1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Printed Material. Book Reviews of An Attic of Ideals, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1968-1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1978-1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Printed Material, 1953-1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Series II: Correspondence, 1964-1997
  This series includes typed and handwritten letters, postcards, greeting cards, original envelopes, and attachments, including photographs. The bulk of the correspondence was received by Karen Swenson but there are a few folders of letters written by Swenson. Folders in boxes 1, 2, and 3 note correspondence with Bruce Berger, Michael Blumenthal, Charles Altieri, [?] Bell, Carol Berge, Robert Boyers, Christopher Brookhouse, Helen Brown, Michael Browne, Jean Burden, John Ciardi, Tony Connor, Mary Crow, George Cuomo, Ki Davis, Richard Eberhart, Kathleen Fraser, Dana Gioia, Jorie Graham, W. S. Graham, Hilda Gregory, Rachel Hadas, Leo Hamalian, Marie Harris, Samuel Hazo, George Hitchcock, Richard Hugo, Lucille Iverson, June Jordan, Donald Justice, George Keithley, X. J. Kennedy, Ismith Kahan, Gallaway Kinnel, Carolyn Kizer, Linda Krenis, Maxine Kumin, Greg Kuzma, Karen Lindsay, Ernest Lookridge, Albert B. Lowenfels, Robert Lowell, Naomi Lazard, Denis Leverton, A. L. Levine, Larry Lieberman, Lyn Lifshin, Pat Madden, Harold Q. Masur, Bill Matthews, Heather McHugh, David Milofsky, Jack Myers, Josephine Nilo, Edward Pennant, Robert Poek, Nilda Raz, M. L. Rosenthal, Stephen Sandy, Reg Saner, Grace Schulman, Peter Sears, Jane Shore, Harry Smith, Kathleen Spirack, Ann Stanford, Ruth Stone, [Mother] Swenson, Helen Susskind, Rawdon Tomlinson, John Updike, John Williams, Martha Winston, Carolyn Wright, Jane Yolen, Al Young, William Zaranke, Betty Kray, Pat Madden, Frank Walker, Elizabeth West, and New York Magazine.
  - Corresp. From, 1978-1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Corresp. From, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Corresp. From, 1976-1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Corresp. From, 1978-1982 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Corresp. From, 1973-1987 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Corresp. From, 1964-1978 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Corresp. From, 1980-1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Corresp. From, 1982-1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Corresp. From, 1973-1981 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Corresp. From, 1968-1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Corresp. From, 1975-1981 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Corresp. From, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Corresp. From, 1974-1981 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Corresp. From, 1973-1985 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Corresp. From, 1976-1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Corresp. From, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Corresp. From, 1973-1982 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Corresp. From, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Corresp. From, 1975-1978 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Corresp. From, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Corresp. From, 1981-1985 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Corresp. From, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Corresp. From, 1977-1980 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Corresp. From, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Corresp. From, 1972-1979 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Corresp. From, 1975-1983 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Corresp. From, 1972-1982 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Corresp. From, 1971-1978 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Corresp. Form, 1976-1985 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Corresp. From, 1980-1985 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Corresp. From, 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Corresp. From, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Corresp. From, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Corresp. From, 1973-1980 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Corresp. From, 1978-1982 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Corresp. From, 1968-1986 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Corresp. From, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Corresp. From, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Corresp. To, 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Corresp. To, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Corresp. To, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1992 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1992-1995 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1989-1997 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1992 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1983-1992 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1997 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1993-1997 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1993-1988 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1991 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1993-1998 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1989-1997 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Series III: Ephemera, 1976-1990
  This series includes poetry reading fliers, a list of fellowship awards, newsletters, and collected poems.
  - Printed Material Misc., undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Printed Material. Poems by Other People, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Printed Material. Broadsides, 1976-1990 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Series IV: Poetry, 1945-1988
  The bulk of the collection, this series includes typed and handwritten poems, and photocopied manuscripts of Swenson's published works. Most of the poems are undated and include Swenson's annotations. This series includes four audiocassettes. Cassette labels indicate three audio recordings of poetry readings and one sample poetry reading.
  - Poems A-ANS, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Poems ANT-AX, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Poems B-Bh, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Poems Bi-Bu, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Poems C, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Poems D, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Poems E, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Poems F-Fl, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Poems Fo-Fu, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Poems G-Go, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Poems Gra-Grou, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Poems H, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Poems I-K, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Poems L-Les, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Poems Let-Lov, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Poems Ma-Mr, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Poems Mo-My, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Poems N, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Poems Pe-Pr, undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Poems R, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Poems S-Sen, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Poems So-Sur, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Poems T, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Poem U-V, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Poems W, undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Poems XYZ, undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Misc. Untitled Poems: Themes of Familial Relations, undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Misc. Untitled Poems: Subjects of Men and Individual Men, 1945, undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Misc. Untitled Poems: On Nature and the Natural, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Misc. Untitled Poems: Themes of Objects and Places, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Misc. Untitled Poems: Subject of Poetry, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Misc. Untitled Poems: Selfhood, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Misc. Unidentified Poems: Subjects of Women and Individual Women, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Misc. Prose, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Poetry, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Poetry, 1980-1989 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Poetry, 1980-1992 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Poetry, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Poetry, 1990-1993 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Poetry, 1989-1991 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Poetry, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Poetry, 1986-1991 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Poetry, 1989-1991 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Early Versions of Asian Poems and Non-Asian Poems, 1985-1998 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Poetry, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - C-D, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - E-F, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - G-K, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - L-M, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - N-O, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - P-R, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Poetry, 1973, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Poetry, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Poetry, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Poetry, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Karen Swenson [audiocassette], undated (Box Shared Fales 006, Folder 1)
  - Karen Swenson, James McKinely [audiocassette], undated (Box Shared Fales 006, Folder 2)
  - Karen Swenson [audiocassette], undated (Box Shared Fales 006, Folder 3)
  - Leftovers and Coldcuts, written and narrated by Lambert Glenn Mendershausen [audiocassette], 1978 (Box Shared Fales 006, Folder 4)
- Series V: Photographs, 1982
  This series includes one photograph of Karen Swenson in a classroom with children and thirteen photographs of people at a gathering in 1982. Swenson is in three of the photographs.
  - Photographs, 1982, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Series VI: Printed Publications, 1967-2006; 6 Linear Feet in 2 manuscript boxes and 5 record cartons.
  This series includes a selection of inscribed publications from Swenson's personal library.
  - Series VI.A.: Printed Publications, 1973-2002
    - Mudfish 4: Contemporary Art and Poetry, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - The American Gentlemen: Social Prestige and the Modern Literary Mind, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - The English Gentleman: Images and Ideas in Literature and Society, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Sex in the Golden Years: What's Ahead May Be Worth Aging For, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Why We Eat What We Eat: How the Encounter Between the New World and the Old Changed the Way Everyone on the Planet Eats, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Rag Mag: A Magazine for New Writings and Graphics, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Arvon International Poetry Competition 1987 Anthology (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Hemingway as a Hunger Artist, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Pivot, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - A Green Place: Modern Poems, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - A Backhanded View of the Law: Irreverent Essays on Justice, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - The Lament of the Single Practitioner: Essays on the Law, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Idaho un Bound: A Scrapbook and Guide, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Idaho un Bound inscription, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Deer Table Legs, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Memoir of the Bookie's Son, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Lonesome Standard Time, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Trickster Makes this World: Mischief, Myth, and Art, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Almost an Island: Travels in Baja California, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - For Mortal Stakes: Solutions for Schools and Society, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Printed publication, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Printed publication, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - The Gift: Imagination and the Erotic Life of Property, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Unravelling the Knot: Poems of Connection, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Canadian Geese and Apple Chatney, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Women of Granite, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Series VI.B.: 2019 Accretion of Printed Publications, 1967-2006
    - The American Dialogue, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - American Weave, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - The Antioch Review, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - The Antioch Review, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Oden, Gloria. Appearances, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Ararat, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Ararat, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Ararat, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Aspen Anthology, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Aspen Anthology, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Aspen Anthology, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Aspen Anthology, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Backtracking: Ancient Art of Southern Idaho, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - The Beloit Poetry Journal - Spring, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - The Beloit Poetry Journal - Winter, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - The Beloit Poetry Journal - Summer, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Blue Unicorn, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - California Quarterly, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Caprice - April, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Caprice - Spring, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - The Carleton Miscellany, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Carolina Quarterly, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Columbia, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Commonweal - February, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Commonweal - May, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Commonweal - July, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Confrontation, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Consumption, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Contemporary Authors, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Colorado Review, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Colorado Review, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Corona, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - The Cream City Review, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Creative Arts Symposium, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Crocodiles in Paradise, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Denver Quarterly - Fall, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Denver Quarterly - Summer, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Denver Quarterly - Winter, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Denver Quarterly - Spring, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Denver Quarterly - Spring, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Denver Quarterly - Fall, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Denver Quarterly - Fall, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Denver Quarterly - Winter, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Diversion - January, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Diversion - October, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Diversion - May, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Epos - Fall, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Epos - Winter, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Epos, undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Folio, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Forbes, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Fragments, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - The Georgia Review, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - The Greenfield Review, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Hawai'I Review, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - The Humanist, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - The International Portland Review, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - John Berryman Studies, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Juniata Voices, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Kansas Quarterly, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Kansas Quarterly, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Kayak, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Kauri January - February, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Kauri March - April, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Kauri May - June, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Kauri September - October, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Kauri, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Lamar Journal of the Humanities, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Literary Cavalcade, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Literary Cavalcade, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Liberation, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Michigan Quarterly Review, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Nation, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Nation, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Nation, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - The New Leader, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - The New Press, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - New Letters, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - New York Poetry, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - The New York Quarterly, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - The New York Quarterly, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - The Niagara Magazine, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Nimrod Fall/Winter, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - The New Yorker, undated (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - The New Yorker - October 18, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - The Paris Review - Spring/Summer, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Pequod - Issue 34, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Pivot - Number 34, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Pivot - Number 36, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Pivot - Number 37, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Pivot - Number 39, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Pivot - Number 40, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Pivot - Number 41, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Pivot - Number 41, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - The Poet's Child, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Poets On: Arriving, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Poets On: Barriers, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Poets On: Nourishment, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Poetry - September 1973 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Poetry - December 1978 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Prairie Schooner - Fall, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Prairie Schooner - Spring, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Prairie Schooner - Fall, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Prairie Schooner - Winter, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Prairie Schooner - Fall, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Prairie Schooner - Spring, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Prairie Schooner - Spring, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Prairie Schooner - Summer, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Prairie Schooner - Spring, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Prairie Schooner - Fall, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Prairie Schooner - Winter, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Prairie Schooner - Spring, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Prairie Schooner - Spring, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Prairie Schooner - Winter, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Prairie Schooner - Winter, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Prairie Schooner - Winter, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Prairie Schooner - Fall, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - The Prospect Review, undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Puerto del Sol, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Puerto del Sol, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Puerto del Sol, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Pulpsmith - Summer, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Pulpsmith - Autumn, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Quarterly Review of Literature, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Rattapallax 7, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Rattapallax 8, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - The Redneck Review of Literature - Fall, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Salmagundi - Winter, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Salmagundi - Spring, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Salmagundi - Fall, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Salmagundi - Spring/Summer, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Salmagundi - Summer, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Saturday Review, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Shenandoah, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Sing Heavenly Muse! - Spring, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - The Slackwater Review - Winter, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - The Slackwater Review - Winter, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Slant, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Snapdragon - Fall, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Snapdragon - Fall, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - The Southern California Anthology - volume 6, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - South Dakota Review - Spring, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - South Dakota Review - Autumn, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - South Dakota Review - Winter, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Southern Poetry Review - Fall, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Southern Poetry Review - Spring, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Southern Poetry Review - Spring, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Southern Poetry Review - Fall, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - The Tenth Muse - Fall, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Thirteenth Moon, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Thirteenth Moon, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Untitled, undated (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Weber - Spring/Summer, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 26)